Yakant Idol
Well, it's early and it's the ending.
Do you have any news from Mr. Serif?
Yes, I do. I have an announcement,
On Wednesday, June 21, we will be releasing our first major single.
Since we are releasing it, JESS is currently in the middle of its release event period,
I'll be in Kanto and other cities,
I hope you have a chance to come to the Kanto area,
If you have a chance to come to Kanto or if you live near Kanto, please come and play with us.
Wow, what kind of song is it? What kind of songs are they?
All of them are in the style of "Ukka",
But there are songs that push me forward,
There was one song that I thought was very difficult when I sang it,
What is the word for that?
How would you put it?
Natural?
What's the word?
I don't know.
There's a song that has a natural feel to it,
A song that feels natural?
Or a song that pushes you forward.
Songs that push you,
Do you have a song that pushes you?
Something natural.
Like, "Just keep your feet on the floor" or something like that?
Recording was difficult for me.
But I think it will grow and develop over the course of the release period,
I hope you can see that.
I would like you to see that.
So it becomes an event even if you are performing live with your fans?
That's right. We do fan live shows and take two-shots.
Taking two-shots.
Smudgeon.
Yes, that's right. I understand.
Now, then...
Yes. I'll be doing a one-man show.
What?
September 30, Shibuya Beats.
October 14, Saturday, Tokyo Kinema Club.
After the new year, it will be at Ebisu Liquid Room on Sunday, January 21 next year.
Great!
Will each of the three have a different concept?
It's still a ways off.
The common goal for all three shows is to sell out every show,
Sell out all the shows.
That's the goal,
Our goal for the spring tour from February to April was to sell out all the shows,
But only one show was sold out.
I see.
So this is not revenge for that.
I really want to sell out this tour.
So you'll be holding release events before then?
I'm hoping to have more and more customers at the release event.
October 14th, and after the new year, January 21st.
As for this...
We're really putting our best foot forward.
I'm putting my money on it.
You are.
You're really on it, aren't you?
And now, for the last time...
I have a cup of tea to cheer you up.
I have a cup of tea for you.
Thank you.
Would you like some tea?
I love tea.
Really?
Bon appétit.
Yes, thank you.
Today we have Sayama tea.
Sayama tea?
Do you know it? There's a tea farm in Saitama Prefecture.
Yes, sir.
I see.
Good. Please go home and know one thing about it.
I understand. The Sayama tea was delicious.
Was it good? Thank you.
Now, then, to the customers.
You know, we have to sell these out now.
That's right.
With your biggest careless smile.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
I would like you to close the program.
Yes, I'm usually careless.
I'm usually careless, but I'll do my best to show cool parts and cute parts in the live performance.
I will do my best to show you my cool and cute side, so please come and see me.
Please come and see us, even if it is just for one show.
Thank you very much. Vibeylon.
This show is,
Mr. Daisuke
Shuhei
Mr. Issei
Mr. Tomonka
provided by Mr. Hideki.
Thank you very much!
Vibyron!